hey everybody welcome to this b1 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to train your listening and
comprehension as I speak so today I'm
gonna talk about the beach this is a
subject that most people like because
most people like the beach but I would
say that I'm actually in that small
minority of people that don't really
love the beach
I'd say that I sometimes like going to
the beach but honestly I prefer other
types of terrain but I'll get back to
that later let's talk about all the cool
beach activities that you can do first
of all there are a ton of cool sports
that can be played in the sand like
volleyball soccer football etc I've got
to say that even though I'm not all that
crazy about the beach beach volleyball
is one of the sports that I love the
most
there's just something about moving and
diving around in the sand that I really
like and I'm fairly tall so I have the
advantage of being able to spike the
ball over the net which is pretty fun
soccer and football can also be fun to
play on the beach but for me I think I
prefer to play those sports on normal
grass it's just easier to move around
it's flat and you can play on a bigger
field so besides sports of course one of
the other things that people do on the
sand is sunbathe now this is something
that I could never do in a million years
because I burned super easily if you put
me out in the Sun for a few hours I'd
come back looking like a ripe tomato no
joke I'm sure some of you might say
something similar some of us get a nice
tan when we're out in the Sun and some
of us burn badly I remember one of my
all-time worst sunburns was when I went
on a pretty long bike ride wearing a
sleeveless shirt it was kind of cloudy
outside so I didn't think I needed
sunscreen and boy was I wrong
my arms were peeling for a long time
after that day okay so back to the beach
let's talk about some of the different
water activities now growing up I did
some boogie boarding which I actually
find pretty fun it just doesn't look as
cool as surfing if you've never been
boogie boarding before it's when you
have a rectangular board and you lie
down on it and when a big wave comes it
pushes you into the shore it's pretty
fun I've actually been thinking about
learning to surf recently because I've
had a few different students who are
surfers and they
talk to me about it and made it sound
pretty cool so maybe I might try it but
I don't think I'd be that good at it
besides surfing and boogie-boarding
there are also some other more exotic
looking activities like kite surfing and
windsurfing and some boat activities
like jet skiing or sailing I have been
sailing before but on the bay not in the
ocean sailing is something that would be
cool to get into but it takes a lot of
practice training and dedication and so
I don't think I'll ever go that route
alright so I mentioned earlier that I'm
not a big beach guy and that's mainly
for two reasons the first is the Sun I
burn easily and the second is that if I
have free time I prefer to go to other
places like the mountain the forest the
countryside even the desert so it's not
that I don't like the beach I just like
other nature places better but despite
that fact I've lived close to the beach
for most of my life and I know I'm lucky
for that alright so that's all for today
leave a comment and tell me some of the
things that you like doing at the beach
I'll see you next video
[Music]
[Applause]